It's good.
إنه جيد.
You blend in with the local aunties.
تندمجين مع السيدات المحليات.
Have something to eat first.
تناول شيئًا ما أولًا.
My Lord,
يا سيدي،
the man who killed you yesterday has been found.
تم العثور على الرجل الذي قتلك بالأمس.
They are under the command of A K.
إنهم تحت قيادة أ. ك.
They got an order from the domestic.
لقد تلقوا طلبية من شركة محلية.
I know. These people
أعرف. هؤلاء الناس
have been hunting me for years.
يطاردونني منذ سنوات.
Why didn't you go to
لماذا لم تذهب إلى
our own turf yesterday?
أرضنا بالأمس؟
It's too dangerous to go to K's place.
من الخطورة بمكان الذهاب إلى منزل كاي.
I'm hungry. I want to eat.
أنا جائع. أريد أن آكل.
It's really delicious.
إنه لذيذ حقاً.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Just send someone to follow them.
أرسل شخصًا ما لمتابعتهم.
Book two more tickets to return home tomorrow.
احجز تذكرتين إضافيتين للعودة إلى الوطن غداً.
Okay. I'll arrange it right away.
حسناً. سأرتب الأمر على الفور.
This... Isn't this...
هذا... أليس هذا...
Speak less.
قلل من الكلام.
Okay.
تمام.
It tastes a bit strange,
طعمه غريب بعض الشيء،
but I like it.
لكنني أحب ذلك.
Ah,
أوه،
you guys finally came back.
لقد عدتم أخيراً.
I couldn't reach you.
لم أتمكن من الوصول إليك.
How are you? Are you hurt?
كيف حالك؟ هل أنت مصاب؟
I am.
أنا أكون.
My eyes are hurt.
عيناي تؤلمني.
We're fine,
نحن بخير،
but
لكن
we didn't get the investment deal.
لم نحصل على صفقة الاستثمار.
We missed the time.
لقد فاتنا الوقت.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
As long as you're okay.
طالما أنك بخير.
Two hundred million is nothing
مئتا مليون لا شيء
for the company.
للشركة.
This company
هذه الشركة
is very powerful in the industry.
يتمتع بنفوذ كبير في هذا المجال.
If we have their support,
إذا حظينا بدعمهم،
our chances of winning against Lin Group
فرصنا في الفوز على مجموعة لين
will be greater.
سيكون أكبر.
Well,
حسنًا،
if there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
I'll be on my way.
سأذهب الآن.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
I'll take you home.
سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
No need.
لا حاجة.
What's going on with you two?
ما الذي يحدث بينكما؟
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
they've landed safely.
لقد هبطوا بسلام.
After all these years,
بعد كل هذه السنوات،
he's still like a loach,
لا يزال مثل سمكة اللوتش،
slipping around everywhere.
يتسلل في كل مكان.
He seems to have a certain influence
يبدو أن له نفوذاً معيناً
in Southeast Asia.
في جنوب شرق آسيا.
It's not as simple as we thought.
الأمر ليس بالبساطة التي كنا نظنها.
Keep an eye on them.
راقبهم جيداً.
Yes.
نعم.
The bid qualification of Yuan Meng Group
تأهيل مجموعة يوان مينغ للمناقصة
should be fine.
لا بأس.
But we don't know what tricks
لكننا لا نعرف ما هي الخدع
Lin Mojiao will play.
ستلعب لين موجياو.
He can kill people directly.
بإمكانه قتل الناس مباشرة.
He has no bottom line.
ليس لديه حدود دنيا.
In addition to holding the land,
بالإضافة إلى امتلاك الأرض،
we need to find evidence of his crimes.
نحن بحاجة إلى إيجاد أدلة على جرائمه.
How's the plan going?
كيف تسير الخطة؟
Why haven't you been in touch lately?
لماذا لم تتواصل معي مؤخراً؟
I ran into some trouble in Thailand.
واجهت بعض المشاكل في تايلاند.
Lin Mojiao made a move.
قام لين موجياو بخطوة.
I lost my phone.
لقد فقدت هاتفي.
Are you injured?
هل أنت مصاب؟
Did anything happen?
هل حدث أي شيء؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I turned danger into safety.
لقد حولت الخطر إلى أمان.
I've returned to the Lin family.
لقد عدت إلى عائلة لين.
The plan remains unchanged.
الخطة لم تتغير.
So perfunctory.
سطحي للغاية.
You didn't treat me like this before.
لم تعاملني هكذا من قبل.
Are you asleep?
هل أنت نائم؟
She's hooked.
لقد أصبحت مدمنة.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Your necklace.
قلادتك.
Anything else?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر؟
No.
لا.
Okay.
تمام.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I only do this to you.
أنا أفعل هذا من أجلك أنت فقط.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
It was just a moment of passion that day.
لقد كانت مجرد لحظة شغف في ذلك اليوم.
We are all adults.
كلنا بالغون.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
About that day,
عن ذلك اليوم،
do you just pretend it never happened?
هل تتظاهر ببساطة بأن الأمر لم يحدث قط؟
Lin Moxiao will come back at any time.
سيعود لين موكسياو في أي وقت.
Answer my question.
أجب عن سؤالي.
Do you pretend it never happened?
هل تتظاهر بأن ذلك لم يحدث أبداً؟
Or what?
أو ماذا؟
We are all adults.
كلنا بالغون.
And
و
I'm your sister-in-law.
أنا زوجة أخيك.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Go home.
اذهب إلى المنزل.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What do you think I'm doing?
ما رأيك فيما أفعله؟
Go away.
يبتعد.
Lin Mojiao will be back soon.
ستعود لين موجياو قريباً.
Use and discard.
استخدمه ثم تخلص منه.
How heartless.
يا له من قسوة!